WILLIAM JARVIS-CROSS

will.jarviscross@mail.utoronto.ca. · 226-260-5073 · 113 Madison Ave. M5R 2S3

My LinkedIn · My Website · My Github

Dedicated employee who loves to work as part of a team. Strong background in coding languages such as Python, Java, C#, JavaScript, and SQL and is excited to work with experienced people and learn new things. Extensive experience working with Object Oriented Programming and problem solving.

EXPERIENCE

MAY 2022 - MAY 2023

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN, SNAPCOMMERCE

Developed features for new and current products along with conducted experiments to efficiently improve the business. Used JavaScript React, Node.js, Python, and many other resources.

APR 2021 - AUG 2021

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN, GEOPOGO

Heavily involved in designing software for Geopogo including augmented reality and general game features. Did front-end and back-end work mostly using Unity and C#.

JAVA POKEMON PROJECT

Worked on a <u>Java Pokémon project</u> with multiple maps, randomly spawning Pokémon, battle scenes, and much more.

EDUCATION

SEP 2019 - APR 2024

BACHELOR OF ARTS AND SCIENCE, UNIVERSITY OF TORONTO

- Fourth year student completing a double major in Computer Science and Astronomy and Astrophysics with a minor in Mathematics.
- Currently have a GPA of 3.84.

RELEVENT UNIVERSITY COURSES TAKEN

- Data Structures and Analysis
- Software Design

- Mathematical Reasoning for Computer Science
- Artificial Intelligence

SKILLS

- Python, Java, C#
- JavaScript, React
- Problem Solving
- Quick Learning
- Object Oriented Programming
- Microsoft Excel and Word